const WordBuilding = {
	level: "b1",
	topic: "Word Building 1",
	lesson_number: 1,

	question_type: "word_building", // ENUM: "file", "video", "audio"
	questions: [
		{
			question: "Money can't buy you ______ or at least that's what some people say.",
			word: "happy",
			answers: "happiness",
		},
		{
			question: "I don't think guns _______ toys for are young children.",
			word: "suit",
			answers: "suitable",
		},
		{
			question: `Alexander Graham Bell developed the first telephone in 1876. Did he have any idea how
      important his _______ would become?`,
			word: "invent",
			answers: "invention",
		},
		{
			question: `Come on! You can do it! There's no such word as _______.`,
			word: "possible",
			answers: "possibility",
		},
		{
			question: `The tobacco companies understood the _______ effects of smoking for
      a long time - but kept quiet about them.`,
			word: "harm",
			answers: "harmful",
		},
		{
			question: `Towards the end of the 20th century, Microsoft became the world's most _______ company.`,
			word: "success",
			answers: "successful",
		},
		{
			question: `Kate Winslet's ______ is the only good thing about this film.`,
			word: "perform",
			answers: "performance",
		},
		{
			question: `The England football team has some talent,
      but we're all _______ about their chances in the World Cup.`,
			word: "doubt",
			answers: "doubtful",
		},
		{
			question: `Frightened? I was absolutely _______!`,
			word: "terror",
			answers: "terrified",
		},
		{
			question: `Adam is too ______ Al I said was I didn't like his new hair colour, and now he won't speak to me.`,
			word: "sense",
			answers: "sensitive",
		},
		{
			question: `I was kept ______ last night by another crazy party in the flat below me.`,
			word: "wake",
			answers: "awake",
		},
		{
			question: `You have a problem, and I'm very ______. But I'm not in a position to lend you money.`,
			word: "sympathy",
			answers: "sympathetic",
		},
	],
}

const Vocabulary_1 = {
	lesson_number: 1,
	level: "b1",
	type: "verb",
	topic: "General",
	vocabularies: [
		{
			word: "happy",
			synonyms: ["joyful", "content", "delighted"],
			definition: "feeling or showing pleasure, contentment, or joy",
			antonyms: ["sad", "miserable", "unhappy"],
			example: "She was extremely happy when she received the news of her promotion.",
		},
		{
			word: "suit",
			definition:
				"to be appropriate or suitable for someone or something; to meet the needs or preferences of someone or something",
			synonyms: ["fit", "match", "complement"],
			antonyms: ["mismatch", "clash", "disagree"],
			example: "He wore a stylish suit to the wedding.",
		},
		{
			word: "invent",
			synonyms: ["create", "devise", "concoct"],
			definition: "create or design (something that has not existed before); be the originator of",
			antonyms: ["destroy", "abolish", "eliminate"],
			example: "Thomas Edison invented the phonograph.",
		},
		{
			word: "possible",
			synonyms: ["feasible", "achievable", "attainable"],
			definition: "able to be done; within the power or capacity of someone or something",
			antonyms: ["impossible", "unattainable", "infeasible"],
			example: "With hard work and determination, anything is possible.",
		},
		{
			word: "harm",
			synonyms: ["damage", "injury", "hurt"],
			definition: "physical injury, especially that which is deliberately inflicted",
			antonyms: ["heal", "protect", "benefit"],
			example: "Please be careful not to harm yourself.",
		},
		{
			word: "success",
			definition: "the accomplishment of an aim or purpose",
			synonyms: ["achievement", "victory", "triumph"],
			antonyms: ["failure", "defeat", "loss"],
			example: "His hard work and dedication led to great success.",
		},
		{
			word: "perform",
			definition: "carry out, accomplish, or fulfill (an action, task, or function)",
			synonyms: ["execute", "carry out", "accomplish"],
			antonyms: ["neglect", "fail", "underperform"],
			example: "The band will perform live at the concert tonight.",
		},
		{
			word: "doubt",
			definition: "a feeling of uncertainty or lack of conviction",
			synonyms: ["uncertainty", "skepticism", "question"],
			antonyms: ["certainty", "belief", "confidence"],
			example: "I have no doubt that she will succeed in her endeavors.",
		},
		{
			word: "sympathy",
			definition:
				"a feeling or expression of understanding, compassion, or sorrow for someone else's hardships, pain, or loss",
			synonyms: ["compassion", "empathy", "understanding"],
			antonyms: ["apathy", "indifference", "unsympathetic"],
			example: "She showed sympathy towards her friend who was going through a difficult time.",
		},
	],
}

const Vocabulary_2 = {
	lesson_number: 2,
	level: "b1",
	type: "verb",
	topic: "Family",

	vocabularies: [
		{
			word: "love",
			synonyms: ["adore", "cherish", "care for"],
			definition: "to have a strong affection or deep emotional attachment for someone",
			antonyms: ["hate", "dislike", "detest"],
			example: "I love spending time with my family.",
		},
		{
			word: "support",
			synonyms: ["encourage", "uphold", "assist"],
			definition: "to provide assistance, encouragement, or help to someone",
			antonyms: ["oppose", "discourage", "hinder"],
			example: "My family always supports me in pursuing my dreams.",
		},
		{
			word: "care",
			synonyms: ["concern", "attention", "regard"],
			definition: "to feel concern or interest for the well-being of someone",
			antonyms: ["neglect", "disregard", "ignore"],
			example: "My parents take great care of me.",
		},
		{
			word: "bond",
			synonyms: ["connection", "tie", "relationship"],
			definition: "a strong emotional connection or relationship between people",
			antonyms: ["distance", "separation", "estrangement"],
			example: "There is a strong bond between siblings.",
		},
		{
			word: "trust",
			synonyms: ["confidence", "reliance", "faith"],
			definition: "a firm belief in the reliability, truth, or ability of someone",
			antonyms: ["distrust", "suspicion", "doubt"],
			example: "I trust my family completely.",
		},
		{
			word: "communicate",
			synonyms: ["convey", "express", "share"],
			definition: "to exchange information, ideas, or feelings with others",
			antonyms: ["miscommunicate", "withhold", "conceal"],
			example: "Open and honest communication is important in a family.",
		},
		{
			word: "respect",
			synonyms: ["admiration", "esteem", "regard"],
			definition: "to have a high or deep regard for someone; to show consideration and honor",
			antonyms: ["disrespect", "disregard", "contempt"],
			example: "Respect is essential in maintaining a healthy family relationship.",
		},
		{
			word: "supportive",
			synonyms: ["encouraging", "helpful", "reliable"],
			definition: "providing assistance, encouragement, or comfort to someone",
			antonyms: ["unsupportive", "unhelpful", "indifferent"],
			example: "My family is always supportive of my decisions.",
		},
		{
			word: "unconditional",
			synonyms: ["absolute", "complete", "unrestricted"],
			definition: "not limited by conditions or requirements; without limitations or expectations",
			antonyms: ["conditional", "limited", "restrictive"],
			example: "A parent's love is often described as unconditional.",
		},
	],
}

const WordBuilding2 = {
	level: "b1",
	topic: "Word Building 2",
	lesson_number: 2,
	question_type: "word_building", // ENUM: "file", "video", "audio"
	questions: [
		{
			question: "There is a lot of ______in the street. Are we missing something?.",
			word: "ACTIVE",
			answers: "activity",
		},
		{
			question: "There are _______ reasons not to fall in love.",
			word: "COUNT",
			answers: "countless",
		},
		{
			question: `Don't ask. I'm afraid I'm _______ to help you.`,
			word: "POWER",
			answers: "powerless",
		},
		{
			question: `I'd love to, but _______ I can't make it this FORTUNE TV hardware weekend.`,
			word: "FORTUNE",
			answers: "unfortunately",
		},
		{
			question: `Just what is the _______ of listening to four old men playing rock music?.`,
			word: "ATTRACT",
			answers: "attraction",
		},
		{
			question: `Safety is not my _______. Speak to my supervisor.`,
			word: "RESPONSE",
			answers: "responsibility",
		},
		{
			question: `Clean it up now. It' ______ ,and sooner or later somebody will fall over.`,
			word: "SLIP",
			answers: "slippery",
		},
		{
			question: `'I've been concerned about your _______ for some time,' the head teacher said in a rather
			threatening voice.`,
			word: "BEHAVE",
			answers: "behavior",
		},
		{
			question: `What do we want? _______! When do we want it? Now!`,
			word: "EQUAL",
			answers: "equality",
		},
	],
}

const Vocabulary_3 = {
	lesson_number: 3,
	level: "b1",
	type: "verb",
	topic: "Adventure",
	vocabularies: [
		{
			word: "adventure",
			synonyms: ["explore", "venture", "discover"],
			antonyms: ["avoid", "stay", "shun"],
			definition: "to engage in exciting and often risky or daring experiences or journeys",
			example: "They embarked on an exciting adventure to explore the uncharted island.",
		},
		{
			word: "thrill",
			synonyms: ["excite", "enthral", "exhilarate"],
			antonyms: ["bore", "disappoint", "depress"],
			definition: "to cause intense excitement, enjoyment, or exhilaration",
			example: "The roller coaster ride thrilled and exhilarated the passengers.",
		},
		{
			word: "explore",
			synonyms: ["discover", "investigate", "traverse"],
			antonyms: ["ignore", "neglect", "overlook"],
			definition: "to travel through or investigate new and unfamiliar places",
			example: "They set out to explore the dense rainforest and discover its hidden treasures.",
		},
		{
			word: "wanderlust",
			synonyms: ["roam", "adventure", "explore"],
			antonyms: ["settled", "contentment", "homebody"],
			definition: "a strong desire to travel and explore the world",
			example: "Her wanderlust led her on countless adventures to far-off lands.",
		},
		{
			word: "expedition",
			synonyms: ["trek", "quest", "journey"],
			antonyms: ["return", "retrace", "retreat"],
			definition: "a journey or excursion undertaken for a specific purpose, often involving exploration or research",
			example: "The scientific expedition aimed to explore the unexplored depths of the ocean.",
		},
		{
			word: "courage",
			synonyms: ["bravery", "fearlessness", "valor"],
			antonyms: ["fear", "timidity", "cowardice"],
			definition: "the ability to face and overcome challenges and danger",
			example: "Their courage allowed them to conquer the treacherous mountain peak.",
		},
		{
			word: "quest",
			synonyms: ["pursuit", "search", "mission"],
			antonyms: ["settle", "acceptance", "resignation"],
			definition: "a journey or mission undertaken in search of something valuable or significant",
			example: "He embarked on a quest to find the legendary treasure hidden in the ancient ruins.",
		},
		{
			word: "daring",
			synonyms: ["bold", "courageous", "fearless"],
			antonyms: ["cautious", "timid", "timid"],
			definition: "willing to take risks and face challenges",
			example: "Their daring spirit led them to attempt the dangerous rock-climbing expedition.",
		},
		{
			word: "explorer",
			synonyms: ["adventurer", "pioneer", "trailblazer"],
			antonyms: ["homebody", "non-adventurer", "settler"],
			definition: "a person who travels to new or unknown places in search of adventure or discovery",
			example: "The famous explorer ventured into uncharted territories and mapped unknown lands.",
		},
	],
}

const WordBuilding3 = {
	level: "b1",
	topic: "Word Building 3",
	lesson_number: 3,
	question_type: "word_building",
	questions: [
		{
			question: "The American War of is known in the USA as the Revolution.",
			word: "DEPEND",
			answers: "independence",
		},
		{
			question: "Medical treatment in the USA depends on your _______ to pay.",
			word: "ABLE",
			answers: "ability",
		},
		{
			question: `They said I was _______ to be a school governor, just because I have a criminal record.`,
			word: "FIT",
			answers: "unfit",
		},
		{
			question: `He looks hideous, but he has a great _______ .`,
			word: "PERSON",
			answers: "personality",
		},
		{
			question: `It was rather _______ of you to leave both your children on the bus.`,
			word: "CARE",
			answers: "careless",
		},
		{
			question: `I spent my _______ in a small town where even the cats and dogs were bored.`,
			word: "CHILD",
			answers: "childhood",
		},
		{
			question: `This advert was filmed in a ______ old factory.`,
			word: "USE",
			answers: "disused",
		},
		{
			question: `Don't accuse me of _______ . You are the
			hypocrite.`,
			word: "HYPOCRITE",
			answers: "hypocrisy",
		},
		{
			question: `These poor chickens are kept in very _______ conditions`,
			word: "NATURE ",
			answers: "unnatural",
		},
	],
}

const Vocabulary_4 = {
	lesson_number: 4,
	level: "b1",
	type: "verb",
	topic: "Food",
	vocabularies: [
		{
			word: "appetite",
			synonyms: ["hunger", "craving", "desire"],
			antonyms: ["satiety", "fullness", "lack of appetite"],
			definition: "A strong desire or craving for food.",
			example: "After a long day, I had a big appetite and enjoyed a hearty meal.",
		},
		{
			word: "delicious",
			synonyms: ["tasty", "yummy", "flavorful"],
			antonyms: ["disgusting", "unappetizing", "unpalatable"],
			definition: "Having a pleasant taste or flavor that is highly enjoyable.",
			example: "The pizza was delicious, with a perfect combination of cheese and toppings.",
		},
		{
			word: "menu",
			synonyms: ["food list", "dining options", "bill of fare"],
			antonyms: ["limited options", "no menu", "no selection"],
			definition: "A list of dishes available in a restaurant or a meal selection.",
			example: "The restaurant offers a diverse menu, featuring both traditional and innovative dishes.",
		},
		{
			word: "reservation",
			synonyms: ["booking", "appointment", "advance arrangement"],
			antonyms: ["walk-in", "no reservation", "first-come, first-served"],
			definition: "The act of reserving a table or seat at a restaurant in advance.",
			example: "We made a reservation at the restaurant to ensure we would have a table for dinner.",
		},
		{
			word: "waiter",
			synonyms: ["server", "attendant", "waitstaff"],
			antonyms: ["customer", "patron", "diner"],
			definition: "A person who serves customers at a restaurant by taking orders and delivering food and drinks.",
			example: "The waiter was friendly and provided excellent service throughout the meal.",
		},
		{
			word: "chef",
			synonyms: ["cook", "culinarian", "kitchen maestro"],
			antonyms: ["novice cook", "amateur chef", "home cook"],
			definition: "A professional cook who is skilled in preparing and presenting food.",
			example: "The chef prepared a gourmet meal using fresh ingredients and innovative techniques.",
		},
		{
			word: "cuisine",
			synonyms: ["food", "cooking", "culinary style"],
			antonyms: ["non-culinary", "non-food", "non-cooking"],
			definition: "A style or type of cooking characterized by specific ingredients, techniques, and flavors.",
			example: "Italian cuisine is known for its use of fresh ingredients and bold flavors.",
		},
		{
			word: "bill",
			synonyms: ["check", "invoice", "tab"],
			antonyms: ["complimentary", "free", "no charge"],
			definition: "A written statement of the total amount owed for a meal or service at a restaurant.",
			example: "At the end of the meal, the waiter brought the bill for us to review and pay.",
		},
		{
			word: "takeout",
			synonyms: ["takeaway", "to-go", "carryout"],
			antonyms: ["dine-in", "eat-in", "in-house"],
			definition: "Food ordered from a restaurant to be consumed off the premises.",
			example: "We decided to get takeout for dinner and enjoyed our meal at home.",
		},
	],
}

const WordBuilding4 = {
	level: "b1",
	topic: "Phrasal verbs 1",
	lesson_number: 4,
	question_type: "phrasal_verbs",
	task: `
	Replace the words in brackets with a suitable phrasal verb. Put the verbs in the right form.
	
		1. look into
		2. held up 
		3. go in for 
		4. check out 
		5. get over 
		6. go along with 
		7. come up with 
		8. called off
	`,
	questions: [
		{
			question: `Karen, I'd like you to _____ from a client. It seems quite serious.`,
			word: "examine",
			answers: "look into",
		},
		{
			question: "Hey! Just _______ this new MP3 player. The sound quality is great.",
			word: "try",
			answers: "check out",
		},
		{
			question: `Yes, I will _______ that.`,
			word: "accept",
			answers: "go along with",
		},
		{
			question: `Because of a really heavy downpour, the party in the park had be _______ .`,
			word: "cancelled",
			answers: "called off",
		},
		{
			question: `Why don't you _______ the 'Weirdest Hair Competition'? I am sure you would win it.`,
			word: "enter",
			answers: "go in for",
		},
		{
			question: `I wonder who first _______ the idea of air-bags in cars?.`,
			word: "thought of",
			answers: "came up with",
		},
		{
			question: `I still haven't really ______ the death of my mother.`,
			word: "recovered from",
			answers: "got over",
		},
		{
			question: `Because of flooding on the line between Brighton and Victoria,
			my train was _______ for several hours.`,
			word: "delayed",
			answers: "held up",
		},
	],
}

export {
	WordBuilding,
	Vocabulary_1,
	Vocabulary_2,
	WordBuilding2,
	Vocabulary_3,
	WordBuilding3,
	Vocabulary_4,
	WordBuilding4,
}
